噢，多麼心痛
Oh, it's murder
當你又用沒事般的口氣訓我
the way you tell me off like it's alright
即使你如何難過
and even at your worst
仍給我力氣繼續
you strengthen my will to fight
你不知道你看上了什麼貨色
And you don't know what you're getting into
我回到家裡最是舒服
I'm feeling right right at home
我就是錯位女王
'Cause I'm the queen of misfits
是你的夢中情人
I'm the stuff of your dreams
我是自己導演
'Cause I declare who I am
眼見不就為真
Everything's not as seems
我要對你施魔咒
I'm gonna put a spell on you
不管你接不接受
and it's a dazzling truth
我會自己找到路
And I can find my way
你的存在無所謂
with or without you
給我聽好
So hear our call
我們要變得家喻戶曉
We're tryna make a name for ourselves
你們曾有機會能跟我
There was a chance that you and I
跟我和好
would be ok
我就是錯位女王
'Cause I'm the queen of misfits
他媽不管你怎麼講
don't give a fuck what you say
我是個超級巨星
'Cause I'm a superstar
得要設法出道
gotta find my own way
本公主很有風度
'Cause I'm the princess of style
跟你說我自有計謀
I got some tricks up my sleeve
我要把你給趕出去
And I'm running you outta town
我要好好地做自己
I gotta be who I wanna be
我就是錯位女王
'Cause I'm the queen of misfits
是你的夢中情人
I'm the stuff of your dreams
我是自己導演
'Cause I declare who I am
眼見不就為真
Everything's not as seems
我要對你施魔咒
I'm gonna put a spell on you
不管你接不接受
and it's a dazzling truth
我會自己找到路
And I can find my way
你的存在無所謂
with or without you
現在看看我們
Take a look at us now
抹掉剛剛的淚水
had to cry for a bit
又回到了最佳狀態
but now we're back on our best
即使看到罪過投影
while you projected the sin
我們在這曾如火燒
There was hell for us here before
現在有差多少？
what's the difference from now?
我們得自己找出路
We had to try and find our way
我們迷路，卻又被找到
We were lost but then were found
我們心裡都有個壞人
And there's a villain in all of us
不過是要個朋友
still needed a friend
每分每秒都是機會
When every moment's a chance for us
來償還以前罪行
to make all our amends
這從一開始就很困難
And it's hard since the start of it
從來就沒簡單過
It's never been easy
你以為我們失去的魔法
And the magic you thought we'd lost
我們靠彼此找回來
It took ourselves while you turned away
給我聽好
So hear our call
我們要變得家喻戶曉
We're tryna make a name for ourselves
你們曾有機會能跟我
There was a chance that you and I
跟我和好
would be ok
我就是錯位女王
'Cause I'm the queen of misfits
他媽不管你怎麼講
don't give a fuck what you say
我是個超級巨星
'Cause I'm a superstar
得要設法出道
gotta find my own way
本公主很有風度
'Cause I'm the princess of style
跟你說我自有計謀
I got some tricks up my sleeve
我要把你給趕出去
And I'm running you outta town
我要好好地做自己
I gotta be who I wanna be
我就是錯位女王
'Cause I'm the queen of misfits
是你的夢中情人
I'm the stuff of your dreams
我是自己導演
'Cause I declare who I am
眼見不就為真
Everything's not as seems
我要對你施魔咒
I'm gonna put a spell on you
不管你接不接受
and it's a dazzling truth
我會自己找到路
And I can find my way
你的存在無所謂
with or without you
我就是錯位女王
'Cause I'm the queen of misfits
他媽不管你怎麼講
don't give a fuck what you say
我是個超級巨星
'Cause I'm a superstar
得要設法出道
gotta find my own way
本公主很有風度
'Cause I'm the princess of style
跟你說我自有計謀
I got some tricks up my sleeve
我要把你給趕出去
And I'm running you outta town
我要好好地做自己
I gotta be who I wanna be